<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NonoConverter</string>

    <string name="title_edit_image_activity">Editing</string>
    <string name="action_convert">Convert</string>
    <string name="action_open_crop">Crop</string>
    <string name="action_open_columns">Columns</string>
    <string name="edit_image_view_description">Convertible image</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_columns">Columns and rows</string>
    <string name="edit_image_columns">Columns</string>
    <string name="edit_image_rows">Rows</string>
    <string name="msg_process_image">Processing image…</string>
    <string name="action_change">Change</string>

    <string name="title_result_activity">Result</string>
    <string name="action_save_thumbnail">Save thumbnail</string>
    <string name="action_save_nonogram">Save nonogram</string>
    <string name="action_home_return">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_home_return">Return home</string>
    <string name="msg_home_return">Are you sure that you want to return home?
        Nonogram will be lost if you don\'t save it.</string>
    <string name="action_return">RETURN</string>
    <string name="action_cancel">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="msg_save_image_done">Image saved:</string>
    <string name="msg_save_image_fail">Failed to save the image</string>
    <string name="msg_func_unavailable">Functionality unavailable</string>
    <string name="action_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_convert">Conversion failed</string>
    <string name="msg_convert">Conversion failed.\nYou can try to change the
        columns count or crop the image.</string>

    <string name="action_load_image">Load Image</string>
    <string name="action_open_about">About</string>
    <string name="action_open_help">Help</string>

    <string name="msg_description">Android mobile application for converting
        images to black-and-white nonogram\n
        - Select an image from the gallery or take a photo\n
        - You can crop selected image\n
        - Select size of nonogram\n
        - Application converts selected image to a nonogram, which has a single
        logical solution\n
        - Save nonogram and its thumbnail
    </string>
    <string name="title_about_activity">About</string>
    <string name="msg_contact">If you have any questions,\nplease contact us:\n
        nonoconverter@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="title_help">Help</string>
    <string name="title_help_info">Information</string>
    <string name="help_info">The process of converting pictures into Japanese
        Crossword is divided into three sections, presented below. To read
        more about each of them, you must click on the icon on the
        left. On each screen (except the main screen), it is possible to go
        back by clicking on the standard \'back\' button in the navigation
        bar or on the \'back\' button in the upper left corner on
        the action bar.</string>
    <string name="title_help_sections">Sections</string>
    <string name="title_help_section_load_image">Load image</string>
    <string name="title_help_section_edit_image">Edit image</string>
    <string name="title_help_section_result">Result</string>
    <string name="help_section_load_image">Upload images from the gallery and
        receive photos from the camera.</string>
    <string name="help_section_edit_image">Rotation, flipping, and cropping
        of a picture. Setting the sizes of the crossword.</string>
    <string name="help_section_result">Viewing and saving the result.</string>
    <string name="help_info_load_image">Before the picture is converted into
        a Japanese Crossword, it needs to be uploaded.</string>
    <string name="title_help_beginning">Beginning</string>
    <string name="help_beginning_load_image">To load an image into the
        application, you need to click on the \'LOAD IMAGE\' button on the
        main screen, then you will go to the screen to select an image.</string>
    <string name="title_help_image_picker">Image picker</string>
    <string name="help_image_picker">All images on the device are presented
        in the form of folders in which they are located. When you
        click on a particular folder, all the images that are in it appear.
        When you click on a specific image, it is loaded into the
        application.\n\nAlso available to receive a photo from the camera. To
        do this, in the upper right corner on the action bar you need to
        click on the camera icon and the camera will open. After that, you
        can take a picture.\n\nAfter selecting an image from the gallery or
        photo, you will be taken to the screen to process the loaded image.
    </string>
    <string name="help_info_edit_image">After loading the image, it can be
        cropped or rotated 90 degrees. To convert an image into the Japanese
        Crossword, you need to set the dimensions of the crossword.</string>
    <string name="help_crop">To crop, rotate and flip the image, click on the
        \'CROP\' button in the lower left corner.\n\nYou can rotate the image
        90, 180 and 270 degrees and flip the image vertically. To do this,
        click on the icons at the bottom.\n\nYou can crop the image by selecting
        the desired rectangle. To fixate your choice, you need to click on the
        check mark in the upper right corner on the action bar</string>
    <string name="help_columns">To set the size of the crossword, click on
        the \'COLUMNS\' button in the lower right corner.\n\nYou can view an
        approximate result. Also you can see current size and range of possible
        sizes after converting above image. There is a slider that provides a
        choice of the number of columns at the bottom of the screen. The number 
        of rows is calculated automatically. There is the selected image for
        conversion in the center of the screen, over of which a grid is drawn.
        To fixate your choice, you need to click on the check mark in the upper
        right corner on the action bar.</string>
    <string name="help_convert">After you have configured everything you need
        to click on \'Convert\' in the upper right corner on the action bar.
        After that, a pop-up window will appear informing you that the
        conversion has begun. You have the opportunity to click on the
        standard \'back\' button in the navigation bar or click on any place
        around the window to cancel the conversion.</string>
    <string name="help_info_result">After converting the image into the
        Japanese Crossword, you can see the result and save it.</string>
    <string name="help_save_thumbnail">You can save the result as a
        thumbnail. The image size in pixels is equal to the size of the
        crossword puzzle. To do this, click on the button \'SAVE THUMBNAIL\'
        in the lower left corner.</string>
    <string name="help_save_nonogram">You can save the result in the form of
        an unsolved Japanese Crossword. To do this, click on the button
        \'SAVE NONOGRAM\' in the lower right corner.</string>
    <string name="help_view_result">You can look at the resulting crossword
        puzzle. In the center of the screen is a solved Japanese Crossword.
        It can be moved and increased or decreased.</string>
    <string name="help_home_return">A quick return to the initial screen is
        available. Just click on the house icon in the upper right corner
        on the action bar.</string>

    <string name="action_rotate">Rotate</string>
    <string name="action_flip">Flip</string>

</resources>
